http://www.avwashington.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.When communicating through our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, or phone number. We may ask for other information as necessary to serve you best.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:* To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)* To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the product, service or information you have requested.Do we use cookies?Yes.  Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.We use cookies to help us remember you and save your preferences for future visits.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
